PATRICK RAYMOND WONG

www.patrwong.com | +1 718-757-1686 | patrickrwong11@gmail.com | www.linkedin.com/in/patrickrwongjr

PROFILE

Adaptable professional with 10 years of valuable work experience. I have a proven history of successful leadership and effective management, building a positive rapport with various clients and colleagues, and using advanced and creative techniques to achieve company goals. I am seeking to utilize my skills and knowledge to secure a position within your company.

EDUCATION AND COURSEWORK

THE PENNSYLVANIA STATE UNIVERSITY, UNIVERSITY PARK, PA B.A. COMMUNICATIONS – MAY 2011

THE WEB DEVELOPER BOOTCAMP, UDEMY
COMPLETED 50 HOUR COURSE WITH CERTIFICATION – MAY 2020

ONLINE CERTIFICATION, FREECODECAMP.ORG
WEB DESIGN, JAVASCRIPT, AND FRONT-END CERTIFICATION – JUNE 2020

SKILLS

- 6 years in Management and Leadership positions overseeing the productivity of teams
- Experienced in CSS, JavaScript, jQuery, Bootstrap, React, node.js, Dart, Flutter, and Figma design
- Proficiency with Salesforce, Zoom, Calendly, MailChimp, and Microsoft Office
- Native English speaker, Intermediate Spanish speaker, Pre-intermediate Finnish speaker

PREVIOUS WORK EXPERIENCE

CAREER SABBATICAL; HELSINKI, FI - FEBRUARY 2020 - MAY 2020

 Focused on personal development while abroad, and a starting a new career in the field of Web Development and design.

LEAD RECRUITER, SECURITAS; DENVER, CO - APRIL 2019 - FEBRUARY 2020

- Screened and hired qualified candidates for employment utilizing a revitalized recruitment process to showcase the best talented candidates.
- Administered drug testing to abide by the company's Drug Free policy.
- Responsible for implementing on and off-site recruitment fairs to source out potential new hires.

SALES CONSULTANT, TRAVELERS HAVEN; DENVER, CO - JULY 2018 - APRIL 2019

- Converted a high volume of leads into new potential clients using the Salesforce CRM.
- Exceeded daily KPI goals by focusing on building a strong relationship with potential customers
- Maintained good organization of my pipeline of clients throughout the sales process.
- Became a top producer in my first month surpassing my colleagues in closed sales by 87%.

TERRITORY MANAGER, TRAVELERS HAVEN; DENVER, CO - JULY 2016 - JULY 2018

- Forged professional connections and brand loyalty by creating partnerships with Property Management companies and rental properties across the United States and parts of Europe.
- Contributed to reducing company costs by negotiating fees and deposits.
- Compromised fair rates to fit budget requests while allowing optimal margin for sales goals.